wpbookingcalendar.com 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy | Booking Calendar - WordPress plugin

**Privacy Policy**  
Our website address is: https://wpbookingcalendar.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

During sending support request from contact form at our website, we do not store this info at our website, instead of that all info that you have entered in the contact form is sending via email to our website support email address. After we have receiving this email we can reply to email that you was entered in the contact form. So contact form is the same as sending support request by email. Access to support email have only authorized support person(s) of own company. 

### Request update form

Form for requests updates is functioned in the same way as Contact form. 

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Customer contact info relative purchased products

We take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information. We are using authorized reseller FastSpring for processing purchased of our products. We do not store and do not have access to any sensitive data like cards details. Please check privacy policy of FastSpring for more details.  
After processing of your order, we are receiving details about this order to support sale email that is contain this info: IP Address, Customer Name, Email, Phone, Address, Payment type, Purchased product details.  
This info required for future providing support for premium customers and providing updates of purchased products based in updates policy. We never share or sell this contact details with third party services. Access to support sales email have only authorized person(s) of our company.
